CHRISTIAN KAMARGA

Houston, TX | christiankamarga@yahoo.com | (713) 417–5748 | linkedin.com/in/christian-kamarga/

SUMMARY

Self-driven Cisco Certified Network Associate and Cybersecurity postgraduate with 6+ years of experience in Python and leading teams in Information Technology projects. Proven data analytical skills in interpreting data trends for Google Store, reduced overhead for security AI development, knowledgeable in project risk management and vendor reporting, excellent written and verbal communication skills across organizational levels, creative and curious mindset to grow and improve. Open to relocate.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Al Prompt Engineer Intern

SecureTrust Cyber, Houston, TX

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

- Collaborated tasks with team members in weekly Scrum meetings and innovated work processes of securely testing
 code by recommending best programming practices in compliance with regulations and security policies.
- Leveraged Streamlit API calls for monitoring and detecting potential risks and threats to organization's end devices.
- Assisted integration of new personnel in remotely setting up client-side Anaconda environments as needed.

Graduate Teaching Assistant

Jan 2022 - May 2022

University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, TX

- Coordinated responsibilities for 2 database classes and improved performance towards fulfilling security procedures.
- Created detailed instructions for database installation with troubleshooting steps and mitigated overhead and delays.
- Advised 60+ students weekly in compliance with security protocols and policies with experience in Oracle and SQL.

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Information Systems

Dec 2022

University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, TX

Perfect Cumulative GPA 4.0

Relevant Graduate Coursework completed:

- Data Communication & Network Security
- Database Management
- Project Management
- Web & Social Analytics

- Data Warehousing & Business Intelligence
- Management of Information Technology
- System Analysis & Design

Bachelor of Science in University Studies

University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, TX

Dec 2020

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY PROJECTS

GitHub Project Portfolio: chrismakeskode.github.io/projects/

Group Project Management (At Your Doorstep)

Sept 2022 - Dec 2022

Developed and supervised team for implementing a delivery mobile service app. Outlined expectations for risk management and mitigation. Communicated results through PowerPoint for client approval and sign-off.

Google Store E-Commerce Analysis

Jun 2022 – Jul 2022

Analyzed international web traffic patterns of Google Store. Uncovered notable traction among select continents with machine learning models. Provided data-driven suggestions for optimizing prospective marketing campaigns.

Databasing Furniture Store Operations

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

Directed a five-person team for Database Management project. Configured database in SQL of a furniture store. Delivered functioning system capable of accurate retention of transactions, inventory, and personnel.

CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)

May 2024

Cisco

Oracle Certified Associate, Java SE 8 Programmer

Aug 2021

Oracle

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Software Experience: Java, Python, SQL, Tableau, SAS, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint, Word, Cisco Packet Tracer, Linux **Creative Applications:** Adobe Creative Cloud, Clip Studio Paint, Photoshop, Autodesk 3DS Max, JavaFX